Luis Alberto Garnica López



-

311 187 4302



lagl95@hotmail.com



Quinta Concepción #112E Quintas del Valle, Tlajomulco de Zuñiga, Jalisco



https://www.luisgarnica.ml



https://www.linkedin.com/in/lagl95

WHO AM I

Computational Systems Engineer, master's in computer sciences degree, 26 years old.

I love to test myself with different challenges, which have taken me to a better development of my self-learning abilities. In general, I feel that I adapt myself very easily when It is about teamwork.



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

October 2016 -May 2017 (Tepic, Nayarit) Centro de Investigación y Desarrollo en Tecnologías de la Información (CIDETI), which belongs to Instituto Tecnológico de Tepic,

Android & MEAN Developer

Backend using MongoDB, NodeJS and Nginx in a Linux droplet from Digital Ocean. The client mobile app was developed using Java.

August 2017 – January 2018 (Tepic, Nayarit)

MX Global Solutions,

C# Developer

Desktop project, custom software for a coffee company. SQL Server relational database, mostly through Stored Procedures. In this job I worked with Visual C# & SQL Server.

January 2018 – January 2019 (Monterrey, Nuevo León)

Dotech S.A. de C.V.,

Analyst Developer

Several web (Java EE & ASP.NET) and desktop (C#) projects. I worked with Oracle RMS ERP customizations for 7-Eleven. In databases I managed Oracle and MySQL. Agile Development with SCRUM methodology.

Mach 2021 – Currently (Guadalajara,

Dotech S.A. de C.V.,

Testing Automation Engineer

Regression tests automation, using Selenium and Cucumber, for several projects of the Banking and Financing Industry

EDUCATION

2019-2021

Jalisco)

Master in Computer Sciences Tecnológico de Monterrey Monterrey, Nuevo León

2013-2018

Computational Systems Engineer Instituto Tecnológico de Tepic. Tepic. Navarit

2013-2018

Technical degree in computing Centro de Estudios Tecnológicos Industriales y de Servicios #100. Teoic. Navarit

Java

Python C# • • • •

TypeScript
JavaScript

PROGRAMING

LANGUAGES



ABILITIES

- Software Development (Java, C#, Puthon)
- Android Mobile apps development (Java).
- Cross-Platform mobile app development using frameworks (lonic).
- NoSQL Database Administration (MongoDB).
- Relational database administration (Microsoft SQL Server, Oracle, MySQL).
- Control version software experience (Git, Team Foundation Server, Bit Bucket).
- Knowledge in HTML, CSS & JavaScript.
- Basic Knowledge in Linux Operating System
- General Knowledge in Machine Learning.
- Neural Networks (Python/Keras).

DBMS

LANGUAGES

• Spanish: Native

 English: Intermediate/Advanced TOEFL ITP: 643 pts.